

NGO DINH ANH QUANG

Marketing Management

L: +84 946185893M: ngodinhanhquang@gmail.com⊘: linkedin.com/in/anhquang1108/

: Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

ABOUT ME

My colleagues call me Finn. I am a 24-yearold youngster with lots of ambition for my Marketing career path.

Currently, I have ~3 years in Marketing and 3 years in Customer Service, and I'm looking forward to developing myself through potential future careers, including but not limited to Assistant Brand Manager, Brand Specialist, Account Marketing, CRM, Loyalty/Partnership, and R&D. How will I match these roles? 50% Experience, 50% Growth Mindset, and 100% willing-to-learn attitude.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATE

TDTU | 2018 - 2022 Graduate with GPA 7.55

IELTS: 7.5

MOS: average 950

SKILLS

Leadership / PM	****
Analysis / Market R&D	***
Content/Mkt Strategy	★★★★ ☆
Collaboration	****
Communication	****
Creativity	***
Problem-Solving	****
Customer Service	****
Detail Oriented	****

WORK EXPERIENCE

Maztermind | 09.2023 - now

Assistant Brand Manager

Main responsibility: Created and led well-thought-out campaigns (IMC plans) for new product launching, rebranding, and more. Collaborated with stakeholders to ensure sales and branding objectives while executing or supporting in some aspects.

Planning and budgeting (30%):

- Presented & led the IMC plans to the Marketing team and other stakeholders on a monthly & quarterly basis.
- We optimized each campaign's possible revenue and expense to ensure positive ROI > 5 and growth rates above 10%.
- Supported the team and sometimes executed the plans for each channel like Social Media, PR, E-commerce, Store VM, Email Mkt, and Customer Service.

Implementing campaigns (50%):

Skilled in almost all Marketing tasks, I executed & coordinated the activities for the campaigns, including:

- TVC/creative production
- Website UIUX development
- Email marketing / Loyalty retention
- Showroom Visual Merchandising and sales training
- Encouraged paid media optimization
- Event hosting
- Social Media Management
- Content writing
- Negotiated Sponsorship and Partnership
- Coordinated with Operations and Product Developers to streamline customer interests & benefits

Reporting & Analyzing (20%):

- Provided deep analysis tailored to each campaign's results using all possible software (KiotViet, Shopify, Klaviyo, Facebook Dashboard, ...)
- Reported the brand's overall performance in sales and brand love on a monthly/quarterly basis to provide insights for future global market penetration.



NGO DINH ANH QUANG

Marketing Management

\(: +84 946185893

: Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

ACHIEVEMENT

Showroom Opening | 05.2024 | Maztermind

- Led the IMC plan & host the event.
- Secured the partnership with Annam Gourmet & The Warehouse.
- Delivered the campaign within the tight deadline of 1.5 months.

LNY & Bau Cua 2024 campaign | 01.2024 | Maztermind

- Led the IMC plan and surpassed all objectives.
- Secured the partnership with Phung An & Phung Thi.
- TVC productions and delivered the campaign within the tight deadline of 1.5 months.

Website + Loyalty launch & Designer Collab campaign | 05-06..2023 | H&M

- Simultaneously executed the content of both campaigns and collaborated with new departments.
- Inspired the stakeholders via kick-offs and incentives.
- Coordinated with all stakeholders effectively to deliver by deadlines and pushed out the most optimal results.

Realign Brand TOVs with stakeholders | 05-06..2023 | H&M

- Created the copywriting and design guidelines to adapt global content to local preferences.
- Collaborated with the PR Manager to identify key pain points.

Hosted a Fashion Show | 06..2018 | TDTU

- Planned and executed the event as Project Manager with a team of 14 freshers.
- Brought brands closer the university students (Routine, Lahoa, Dered, Matkinhhanghieu)

WORK EXPERIENCE

H&M SEA region | 03.2023 - 08.2023

Brand (Content) Coordinator

Main Responsibility: Joined the office team in 03.2022 as Marketing Support and got promoted to Brand (Content) Coordinator. Essentially, I bring H&M campaigns from global to local, adapting them through content and cultural appropriations for the VN market while also supporting the SG, MY, and PH markets within the region.

Planning and adapting the campaigns (20%):

- Planned with the regional content team on a weekly, monthly, or ad-hoc basis to adapt the global campaigns.
- Collaborated with the local market stakeholders to plan out the content according to local needs.
- Proposed the local add-ons for campaigns

Coordinating the campaigns (60%):

Coordinated with all stakeholders to deliver ATL & BTL plans content-wise to all online and offline channels:

- INTERNAL:
 - Store VM, Distribution Center, Regional Sales team, CS
 - Ecom, Loyalty, and global campaign leader
- EXTERNAL:
 - Paid Media Agency, DOOH & offline media agencies, Print suppliers, Event agencies, landlords,

Executed the campaigns via the continuation of responsibilities from the *Marketing Support role* (see below)

Reporting & Analyzing (20%):

- Analyzed data via the Facebook dashboard, PowerBI, and data from vendors.
- Updated the campaign/brand 360 records and provided key learnings for the team and related departments.



\: +84 946185893
\: ngodinhanhquang@gmail.com
\?: linkedin.com/in/anhquang1108/
\?: Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

HOBBY

Fashion & Art Sports & E-sports Board Games Gaming Industry Automobile Cooking, Gourmet Anime, Animations Coffeeholic

REFERRAL

Tran Mai Phuong | Direct line-manager Title: Group Brand Manager Company: Maztermind

Verzo Nikki | Direct line manager Title: Experience & Operation Manager SEA Company: H&M

Both are available upon request.

WORK EXPERIENCE

H&M SEA region | 03.2022 - 02.2023

Marketing Support

Main Responsibility: Joined when the department was undergoing transformation, everything I did was revamped from the ground up with a focus on execution, way of working, and guidelines adjustment to match the local market needs:

- Plan, write content & manage social media + Online CS
- Design/order assets or content for multiple channels. Ex: Instore POSM, Social image or video, DOOH, Digital, Paid social media, Event, and more.
- Validated & provided translations or alterations for copies of artworks and copywriting.
- Manage budget for Paid social media.
- Monitoring competitors and crises. Tracking data and reports from every channel and providing key learnings for individual periods
- Admin tasks such as contracts, invoices, and government paperwork.

H&M VN | 07.2020 - 02.2023

Sale Advisor (Mentor)

- Trained for the potential next role: Visual Merchandising (Product Display)
- Worked at all HCMC-based stores. (4 total)
- Mentoring new SA
- Responsible for the H&M Lady Sales revenue
- Ensure the best display for the departments.